Institute for First Amendment Studies Records MS074
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Subject files, 1920 -- 1999; 1985 -- 1996; MS074.002; 38.4 Linear Feet
  - Supreme Court- Committee for the Public Education v. Regan, 1980; MS074.002.058.00083 (Box 58)
  - Supreme Court- Congressional Record Senate, 1984; MS074.002.058.00084 (Box 58)
  - Supreme Court- Congressional Record House, 1984; MS074.002.058.00085 (Box 58)
  - Supreme Court- Engel v. Vitale, 1962; MS074.002.058.00086 (Box 58)
  - Supreme Court- Estate of Thorton v. Cador Inc., 1985; MS074.002.058.00087 (Box 58)
  - Supreme Court- Forest Hills v. Grace Baptist, 1988; MS074.002.058.00088 (Box 58)
  - Supreme Court- Gillette v. United States, 1971; MS074.002.058.00089 (Box 58)
  - Supreme Court- Grand Rapids, Michigan v. Ball, 1985; MS074.002.058.00090 (Box 58)
  - Supreme Court- Hernandez v. IRS/Graham v. IRS, 1989; MS074.002.058.00091 (Box 58)
  - Supreme Court- Hunter v. McNair, 1976; MS074.002.058.00092 (Box 58)
  - Supreme COurt- Larkin v. Grendeli Den, 1982; MS074.002.058.00093 (Box 58)
  - Supreme Court- Leman v. Kurtzman, 1971 -- 1994; MS074.002.058.00094 (Box 58)
  - Supreme Court- Levitt v. Committee for Public Education, 1973; MS074.002.058.00095 (Box 58)
  - Supreme Court- Lynch v. Donnelly, 1984; MS074.002.058.00096 (Box 58)
  - Supreme Court- McCollum v. Board of Education, 1948; MS074.002.058.00097 (Box 58)
  - Supreme COurt- Meek v. Pittenger, 1975; MS074.002.058.00098 (Box 58)
  - Supreme Court- Mueller v. Allen, 1983; MS074.002.058.00099 (Box 58)
  - Supreme Court- McCreary v. Stone, 1984; MS074.002.058.00100 (Box 58)
  - Supreme Court- Planned Parenthood v. Casey Decided 6/29/92 (PA Abortion Case), 1992; MS074.002.058.00101 (Box 58)
  - S.C-Religious Symbols on Public Property, 1995; MS074.002.058.00102 (Box 58)
  - Supreme Court- Roemer v. Board of Education, ca, 1976; MS074.002.058.00103 (Box 58)
  - Supreme Court- Rust v. Sullivan Decided May 23, 1988 -- 1991; MS074.002.058.00104 (Box 58)
  - Supreme Court- Schenck v. Pro Choice Network, 1995 -- 1996; MS074.002.058.00105 (Box 58)
  - Supreme Court- Soan v. Leman, 1973; MS074.002.058.00106 (Box 58)
  - Supreme Court- Smith v. Employment Division, Oregon Dpt. of Human Resources v. Smith 485 U.S. 660, 1988; MS074.002.058.00107 (Box 58)
  - Supreme Court- Smith v. Board of School Commission, 1987; MS074.002.058.00108 (Box 58)
  - Supreme Court- Texas Montly v. Bullock, 1989; MS074.002.058.00109 (Box 58)
  - Supreme Court- Tilton v. Richardson, 1971; MS074.002.058.00110 (Box 58)
  - Supreme Court- Walz v. Tax Commission of NY, 1971; MS074.002.058.00111 (Box 58)
  - Supreme COurt- Witters v Washington Department of Services for, 1985 -- 1989; MS074.002.058.00112 (Box 58)
  - Supreme Court-Wolman v. Walter, 1977; MS074.002.059.00001 (Box 59)
  - Supreme Court-Zorach v. Clauson, 1951; MS074.002.059.00002 (Box 59)
  - Supreme Court, NOW v. Scheidler, accepted for review, 1993; MS074.002.059.00003 (Box 59)
  - Supreme Court, RICO, 1994; MS074.002.059.00004 (Box 59)
  - Supreme Court, Epperson v. Arkansas, 1968; MS074.002.059.00005 (Box 59)
  - Supreme Court, Brown v. Woodland Joint Unified School District, 1992; MS074.002.059.00006 (Box 59)
  - Talk radio-NYC, 1989 -- 1994; MS074.002.059.00007 (Box 59)
  - Talk shows, 1988; MS074.002.059.00008 (Box 59)
  - Rabbi Marc Tanenbaum, 1992; MS074.002.059.00009 (Box 59)
  - Tax exemptions, 1991; MS074.002.059.00010 (Box 59)
  - Tax the church, 1984 -- 1992; MS074.002.059.00011 (Box 59)
  - Taxpayers Association, 1995 -- 1996; MS074.002.059.00012 (Box 59)
  - Tax protestors, 1995; MS074.002.059.00013 (Box 59)
  - Teachers for a Democratic Culture, 1994 -- 1995; MS074.002.059.00014 (Box 59)
  - Kevin Tebedo, 1995; MS074.002.059.00015 (Box 59)
  - Teddy Bart Producations, 1989 -- 1992; MS074.002.059.00016 (Box 59)
  - Teenagers, 1984 -- 1989; MS074.002.059.00017 (Box 59)
  - Teen aid, 1991 -- 1993; MS074.002.059.00018 (Box 59)
  - Teen Vision, 1987 -- 1988; MS074.002.059.00019 (Box 59)
  - Telecommunications Act of 1995, MS074.002.059.00020 (Box 59)
  - Televangelists, 1986 -- 1993; MS074.002.059.00021 (Box 59)
  - Televangelists pleas for money, 1987; MS074.002.059.00022 (Box 59)
  - Televangelist summaries, 1984 -- 1986; MS074.002.059.00023 (Box 59)
  - T.V. advertising, 1951; MS074.002.059.00024 (Box 59)
  - Television and morality, 1985 -- 1994; MS074.002.059.00025 (Box 59)
  - Lynne Ann Tempest, 1992; MS074.002.059.00027 (Box 59)
  - Tennessee, 1994 -- 1996; MS074.002.059.00028 (Box 59)
  - Brad Terkleson, 1992; MS074.002.059.00029 (Box 59)
  - Terrorism, 1994; MS074.002.059.00030 (Box 59)
  - Harris County (Texas) Republicans, 1992; MS074.002.059.00031 (Box 59)
  - Domestic terrorism, 1995; MS074.002.059.00032 (Box 59)
  - Randall Terry (see Operation Rescue), 1991 -- 1993; MS074.002.059.00033 (Box 59)
  - Texas, 1991 -- 1996; MS074.002.059.00034 (Box 59)
  - Texas/Democrats for Life, 1995; MS074.002.059.00035 (Box 59)
  - FYI, Texas, 1995; MS074.002.059.00036 (Box 59)
  - Texas Federation of Traditional Republicans, 1992 -- 1994; MS074.002.059.00037 (Box 59)
  - Texas Freedom Alliance, 1995; MS074.002.059.00038 (Box 59)
  - Jack Chambers, Texas, 1993; MS074.002.059.00039 (Box 59)
  - Texas mainstream voters project, 1993; MS074.002.059.00040 (Box 59)
  - Texas Physicians Resource Council, MS074.002.059.00041 (Box 59)
  - Harris County (Texas) Republicans, MS074.002.059.00042 (Box 59)
  - School prayer, Texas, 1995; MS074.002.059.00043 (Box 59)
  - Textbooks--Hawkins County Tennessee, 1985 -- 1987; MS074.002.059.00044 (Box 59)
  - Textbooks, USA, 1985 -- 1989; MS074.002.059.00045 (Box 59)
  - Textbooks, multiculturalism, 1994; MS074.002.059.00046 (Box 59)
  - Cal Thomas, 1983 -- 1996; MS074.002.059.00047 (Box 59)
  - Judge Clarence Thomas, 1996; MS074.002.059.00048 (Box 59)
  - H.A. Thompson, 1992; MS074.002.059.00049 (Box 59)
  - Linda Thompson, 1994 -- 1995; MS074.002.059.00050 (Box 59)
  - Rosemary Thomson, 1981; MS074.002.059.00051 (Box 59)
  - Tikvah, 1992; MS074.002.059.00052 (Box 59)
  - Evangelist Robert Tilton, 1987 -- 1992; MS074.002.059.00053 (Box 59)
  - Lee Tim Ministries, 1994; MS074.002.059.00054 (Box 59)
  - Time Magazine, 1986 -- 1991; MS074.002.059.00055 (Box 59)
  - Herb Titus [1 of 2], 1993 -- 1996; MS074.002.059.00056 (Box 59)
  - Herb Titus [2 of 2], 1993 -- 1994; MS074.002.059.00057 (Box 59)
  - Gary Todd, 1993; MS074.002.059.00058 (Box 59)
  - John Tomasin, Esq., 1995 -- 1996; MS074.002.059.00059 (Box 59)
  - Top ten, MS074.002.059.00060 (Box 59)
  - Bill Torricelli, 1991; MS074.002.059.00061 (Box 59)
  - Arpad Toth, 1992 -- 1994; MS074.002.059.00062 (Box 59)
  - Tracts, MS074.002.059.00063 (Box 59)
  - Tradition, family, property, 1986; MS074.002.059.00064 (Box 59)
  - Tranet, 1993; MS074.002.059.00065 (Box 59)
  - John Trelstad, 1986 -- 1987; MS074.002.059.00066 (Box 59)
  - Trinity Broadcasting Network, 1994; MS074.002.059.00067 (Box 59)
  - Trinity hotline, 800# Christian businesses, MS074.002.059.00068 (Box 59)
  - The Truth, 1994; MS074.002.059.00069 (Box 59)
  - The Truth at Last, 1994; MS074.002.059.00070 (Box 59)
  - Truth Seeker, 1995; MS074.002.059.00071 (Box 59)
  - Keith Tucci, see also Operation Rescue, 1992; MS074.002.059.00072 (Box 59)
  - Turn the Hearts, California, 1992; MS074.002.059.00073 (Box 59)
  - Ted Turner, 1989 -- 1990; MS074.002.059.00074 (Box 59)
  - 2 Live Crew, 1990; MS074.002.059.00075 (Box 59)
  - John Tyndall, MS074.002.059.00076 (Box 59)
  - Underground hotline, 1994 -- 1995; MS074.002.059.00077 (Box 59)
  - UHAC guide, 1978 -- 1992; MS074.002.059.00078 (Box 59)
  - Unification Church, see also "moon", 1987 -- 1995; MS074.002.059.00079 (Box 59)
  - UUSCGP, 1990; MS074.002.059.00080 (Box 59)
  - Unitarian Universalist Church, 1985 -- 1994; MS074.002.059.00081 (Box 59)
  - Unitarian Universalist: brochures, materials, 1988 -- 1994; MS074.002.059.00082 (Box 59)
  - Unitarian Universalist funding program, 1993; MS074.002.059.00083 (Box 59)
  - UU General Assembly 1988, 1987 -- 1990; MS074.002.059.00084 (Box 59)
  - United Messianic Jewish Outreach, 1995; MS074.002.059.00085 (Box 59)
  - US Dept. of Education, 1995; MS074.002.059.00086 (Box 59)
  - Universal Life, 1994; MS074.002.059.00087 (Box 59)
  - University conversion project, 1994; MS074.002.059.00088 (Box 59)
  - Rep. Jolene Unsoeld, 1994; MS074.002.059.00089 (Box 59)
  - John Upton, MS074.002.059.00090 (Box 59)
  - Urantia, 1991; MS074.002.059.00091 (Box 59)
  - Urban assault, 1992; MS074.002.059.00092 (Box 59)
  - USA Today, 1990; MS074.002.059.00093 (Box 59)
  - US Council for World Freedom, MS074.002.059.00094 (Box 59)
  - US Taxpayers Party, 1994 -- 1996; MS074.002.059.00095 (Box 59)
  - Utah, 1992 -- 1995; MS074.002.059.00096 (Box 59)
  - U turn, 1996; MS074.002.059.00097 (Box 59)
  - Values, 1984 -- 1992; MS074.002.059.00098 (Box 59)
  - Values through media, 1995; MS074.002.059.00099 (Box 59)
  - Values through media [1 of 2], 1992 -- 1993; MS074.002.060.00001 (Box 60)
  - Values through media [2 of 2], 1992 -- 1993; MS074.002.060.00002 (Box 60)
  - Jewel Van der Merwe discernment ministries, 1990 -- 1991; MS074.002.060.00003 (Box 60)
  - Jack Van Impe, 1990 -- 1991; MS074.002.060.00004 (Box 60)
  - Roland Van Liew, 1990 -- 1992; MS074.002.060.00005 (Box 60)
  - Patricia Vanoni (Texas mainstream voters), 1993; MS074.002.060.00006 (Box 60)
  - Vermont, 1994 -- 1995; MS074.002.060.00007 (Box 60)
  - Susan Vernon, 1993; MS074.002.060.00008 (Box 60)
  - Viacom, 1994; MS074.002.060.00009 (Box 60)
  - Richard Viguerie, 1980; MS074.002.060.00010 (Box 60)
  - Vineyard, 1992 -- 1993; MS074.002.060.00011 (Box 60)
  - Virginia, 1995 -- 1996; MS074.002.060.00012 (Box 60)
  - Virginian Pilot/Esther Diskin, MS074.002.060.00013 (Box 60)
  - Voice of Reason, 1987 -- 1993; MS074.002.060.00014 (Box 60)
  - Voter guides, 1996; MS074.002.060.00015 (Box 60)
  - Voters for choice, 1992 -- 1996; MS074.002.060.00016 (Box 60)
  - Voters organized for informed choice in elections, 1995; MS074.002.060.00017 (Box 60)
  - Jeff Voth, 1994; MS074.002.060.00018 (Box 60)
  - Freke Vuijst, 1994; MS074.002.060.00019 (Box 60)
  - WABC--New York City, 1986; MS074.002.060.00020 (Box 60)
  - Waco, 1993; MS074.002.060.00021 (Box 60)
  - Vicky Wade, 1989; MS074.002.060.00022 (Box 60)
  - WADL--Witches Anti-discrimination Lobby, 1995; MS074.002.060.00023 (Box 60)
  - Wake up America, 1994; MS074.002.060.00024 (Box 60)
  - Waldenbooks, 1991; MS074.002.060.00025 (Box 60)
  - Dwayne Walker, 1991 -- 1992; MS074.002.060.00026 (Box 60)
  - Wall builders, 1991 -- 1996; MS074.002.060.00027 (Box 60)
  - Wall Street Underground, 1994; MS074.002.060.00028 (Box 60)
  - Mildred Walton, 1990 -- 1991; MS074.002.060.00029 (Box 60)
  - Pam Walton, 1996; MS074.002.060.00030 (Box 60)
  - Rus Walton (see also Plymouth Rock Foundation), 1994; MS074.002.060.00031 (Box 60)
  - Washington for Jesus, 1988 -- 1996; MS074.002.060.00032 (Box 60)
  - Washington Spectator, 1993 -- 1996; MS074.002.060.00033 (Box 60)
  - Washington Times, 1994; MS074.002.060.00034 (Box 60)
  - Washington Update, 1996; MS074.002.060.00035 (Box 60)
  - Washington Watch, 1990 -- 1996; MS074.002.060.00036 (Box 60)
  - Washington Watch, 1993 -- 1996; MS074.002.060.00037 (Box 60)
  - Washington State, 1984 -- 1994; MS074.002.060.00038 (Box 60)
  - Ruth Watz, 1988; MS074.002.060.00039 (Box 60)
  - The Way, MS074.002.060.00040 (Box 60)
  - Doug Wead, 1990 -- 1992; MS074.002.060.00041 (Box 60)
  - Gloria Weber, 1995; MS074.002.060.00042 (Box 60)
  - Weekly Standard, 1995; MS074.002.060.00043 (Box 60)
  - We are the Weird, 1993; MS074.002.060.00044 (Box 60)
  - Lowell Weicker, 1986; MS074.002.060.00045 (Box 60)
  - Ed Weinberg, 1992; MS074.002.060.00046 (Box 60)
  - Gov. William F. Weld, 1992; MS074.002.060.00047 (Box 60)
  - Welfare, 1994; MS074.002.060.00048 (Box 60)
  - Wellspring, Retreat Resource Center, 1990; MS074.002.060.00049 (Box 60)
  - Bob Wescott for State Rep, 1986; MS074.002.060.00050 (Box 60)
  - Western States Center, 1993 -- 1995; MS074.002.060.00051 (Box 60)
  - West words, 1992; MS074.002.060.00052 (Box 60)
  - Shane Westhoelter, nat'l info net, 1989; MS074.002.060.00053 (Box 60)
  - West Virginia, 1994; MS074.002.060.00054 (Box 60)
  - Paul Weyrich, 1984 -- 1995; MS074.002.060.00055 (Box 60)
  - White Aryan Resistance (WAR), 1990 -- 1991; MS074.002.060.00056 (Box 60)
  - Jeff White, 1994; MS074.002.060.00057 (Box 60)
  - Mel White, 1996; MS074.002.060.00058 (Box 60)
  - Mel White, 1994 -- 1996; MS074.002.060.00059 (Box 60)
  - Willy Whitefeather, 1995; MS074.002.060.00060 (Box 60)
  - Fred Whitehead, 1991 -- 1993; MS074.002.060.00061 (Box 60)
  - John Whitehead, 1982 -- 1994; MS074.002.060.00062 (Box 60)
  - White Rose Banquet, 1996; MS074.002.060.00063 (Box 60)
  - White Supremicists, 1985 -- 1996; MS074.002.060.00064 (Box 60)
  - Whitewater, 1994; MS074.002.060.00065 (Box 60)
  - Dan Whitley, 1995; MS074.002.060.00066 (Box 60)
  - Whole language, 1990 -- 1993; MS074.002.060.00067 (Box 60)
  - Rev. Donald Wildmon, 1989 -- 1993; MS074.002.060.00068 (Box 60)
  - Don Wilkey [1 of 2], 1994; MS074.002.060.00069 (Box 60)
  - Don Wilkey [2of 2], 1994; MS074.002.060.00070 (Box 60)
  - Williamsburg Charter Foundation, 1988; MS074.002.060.00071 (Box 60)
  - Pete Wilson, 1996; MS074.002.060.00072 (Box 60)
  - Adina Wingate-Quijada, 1995; MS074.002.060.00073 (Box 60)
  - Marlene Winell, 1989 -- 1993; MS074.002.060.00074 (Box 60)
  - Ben Winton, 1987 -- 1993; MS074.002.060.00075 (Box 60)
  - Wisconsin, 1992 -- 1995; MS074.002.060.00076 (Box 60)
  - Wise Use Movement, 1996; MS074.002.061.00001 (Box 61)
  - Wise Use Movement, 1992 -- 1993; MS074.002.061.00002 (Box 61)
  - Witchcraft, 1989 -- 1995; MS074.002.061.00003 (Box 61)
  - Witches Anti-discrimination Lobby, 1995; MS074.002.061.00004 (Box 61)
  - Bill Witt, MS074.002.061.00005 (Box 61)
  - Women's project, April 30-May 2, 1993 -- 1994; MS074.002.061.00006 (Box 61)
  - Women's Aglow Fellowship, 1993; MS074.002.061.00007 (Box 61)
  - Women's concerns/issues, 1986 -- 1994; MS074.002.061.00008 (Box 61)
  - Women's Project, 1995; MS074.002.061.00009 (Box 61)
  - Alison Woodhead, 20/20, 1992; MS074.002.061.00010 (Box 61)
  - Woolsey, CIA/Clinton, 1993; MS074.002.061.00011 (Box 61)
  - Workbook, 1992 -- 1994; MS074.002.061.00012 (Box 61)
  - World Anti-Communist League, MS074.002.061.00013 (Box 61)
  - World Evangelism Fellowship, 1989 -- 1990; MS074.002.061.00014 (Box 61)
  - World government, 1994; MS074.002.061.00015 (Box 61)
  - World help, 1992; MS074.002.061.00016 (Box 61)
  - World Jewish Congress, 1988 -- 1996; MS074.002.061.00017 (Box 61)
  - World Magazine (God's World Publication), MS074.002.061.00018 (Box 61)
  - World Vision, 1991; MS074.002.061.00019 (Box 61)
  - Worldwide Church of God, 1984 -- 1985; MS074.002.061.00020 (Box 61)
  - Richard Wurmbrand, 1991; MS074.002.061.00021 (Box 61)
  - Wyoming, 1994 -- 1996; MS074.002.061.00022 (Box 61)
  - Frank Zappa, 1985 -- 1989; MS074.002.061.00023 (Box 61)
  - Rev. David Yonggi Cho, 1992 -- 1995; MS074.002.061.00024 (Box 61)
  - Martin Young, 1988 -- 1992; MS074.002.061.00025 (Box 61)
  - Young America's Foundation, MS074.002.061.00026 (Box 61)
  - Youth Alive, 1986 -- 1988; MS074.002.061.00027 (Box 61)
  - Youth quest, 1996; MS074.002.061.00028 (Box 61)
  - Youth with a mission, 1990; MS074.002.061.00029 (Box 61)
  - Leonard Zeskind, 1990 -- 1993; MS074.002.061.00030 (Box 61)
  - Jarry Zilliox, Jr. (investigator), 1993; MS074.002.061.00031 (Box 61)
  - Zion's hope, 1994 -- 1995; MS074.002.061.00032 (Box 61)
  - Zoning, 1994; MS074.002.061.00033 (Box 61)
  - D. James Kennedy--Coral Ridge Church, correspondence and publications, 1996 -- 1997; MS074.002.061.00034 (Box 61)
  - D. James Kennedy--Coral Ridge Church, 1988 -- 1994; MS074.002.061.00035 (Box 61)
  - D. James Kennedy--Coral Ridge Church, Coral Ridge ministries, 1980 -- 1994; MS074.002.061.00036 (Box 61)
  - D. James Kennedy--Coral Ridge Church, pamphlets [1 of 8], 1997; MS074.002.061.00037 (Box 61)
  - D. James Kennedy--Coral Ridge Church, pamphlets [2 of 8], MS074.002.061.00038 (Box 61)
  - D. James Kennedy--Coral Ridge Church, pamphlets [3 of 8], MS074.002.061.00039 (Box 61)
  - D. James Kennedy--Coral Ridge Church, pamphlets [4 of 8], MS074.002.061.00040 (Box 61)
  - D. James Kennedy--Coral Ridge Church, pamphlets [5 of 8], MS074.002.061.00041 (Box 61)
  - D. James Kennedy--Coral Ridge Church, pamphlets [6 of 8], MS074.002.061.00042 (Box 61)
  - D. James Kennedy--Coral Ridge Church, pamphlets [7 of 8], MS074.002.061.00043 (Box 61)
  - D. James Kennedy--Coral Ridge Church, pamphlets [8 of 8], MS074.002.061.00044 (Box 61)
  - Council for National Policy--meeting packet, 1998; MS074.002.061.00045 (Box 61)
  - Council for National Policy, misc. member info, 1997; MS074.002.061.00046 (Box 61)
  - Council for National Policy, biographies, 1998; MS074.002.061.00047 (Box 61)
  - Council for National Policy--members, 1996; MS074.002.061.00048 (Box 61)
  - Council for National Policy, standing committees, 1995 -- 1996; MS074.002.061.00049 (Box 61)
  - Council for National Policy, members, 1995; MS074.002.061.00050 (Box 61)
  - Council for National Policy, California members, 1996; MS074.002.061.00051 (Box 61)
  - Council for National Poicy - Africa, 1992 -- 1993; MS074.002.061.00052 (Box 61)
  - Council for National Policy, businesses with CNP ties, 1993; MS074.002.061.00053 (Box 61)
  - Council for National Policy, Clinton chronicles, 1993; MS074.002.061.00054 (Box 61)
  - Council for National Policy, addendum to 1996 telephone directory, MS074.002.061.00055 (Box 61)
  - Council for National Policy, Executive Committe and awards list, 1998; MS074.002.061.00056 (Box 61)
  - Council for National Policy, articles and press releases about the CNP, 1998; MS074.002.061.00057 (Box 61)
  - Council for National Policy, articles about the CNP, 1994 -- 1996; MS074.002.061.00058 (Box 61)
  - Council for National Policy, members/bios, 1988; MS074.002.061.00059 (Box 61)
  - Council for National Policy, Beijing UN conference, 1995; MS074.002.061.00060 (Box 61)
  - Council for National Policy, Capitol Hill report, 1995; MS074.002.061.00061 (Box 61)
  - Council for National Policy, Coors Connection, 1993; MS074.002.061.00062 (Box 61)
  - Council for National Policy, Colorado Springs, 1982; MS074.002.061.00063 (Box 61)
  - Council for National Policy, formation of CNP, 1981; MS074.002.061.00064 (Box 61)
  - Council for National Policy, guest biographies, 1993 -- 1996; MS074.002.061.00065 (Box 61)
  - Council for National Policy, headquarters, MS074.002.061.00066 (Box 61)
  - Council for National Policy, McLean, Va., 1995; MS074.002.061.00067 (Box 61)
  - Council for National Policy, member list by state, MS074.002.061.00068 (Box 61)
  - Council for National Policy, membership forms, 1994; MS074.002.061.00069 (Box 61)
  - Council for National Policy, Nashville, 1995; MS074.002.061.00070 (Box 61)
  - Council for National Policy, new member bios, 1995; MS074.002.061.00071 (Box 61)
  - Council for National Policy, New Orleans, 1994 -- 1995; MS074.002.062.00001 (Box 62)
  - Council for National Policy, 990s, 1995; MS074.002.062.00002 (Box 62)
  - Council for National Policy, organization, 1988 -- 1989; MS074.002.062.00003 (Box 62)
  - Council for National Policy, Orlando, Mar., 1996; MS074.002.062.00004 (Box 62)
  - Council for National Policy, Palm Springs, 1995; MS074.002.062.00005 (Box 62)
  - Council for National Policy, Howard Phillips, 1996; MS074.002.062.00006 (Box 62)
  - Council for National Policy, pornography, MS074.002.062.00007 (Box 62)
  - Council for National Policy, St. Louis, 1993; MS074.002.062.00008 (Box 62)
  - Council for National Policy, St. Louis/materials distributed, 1993; MS074.002.062.00009 (Box 62)
  - Council for National Policy, seating lists, 1995; MS074.002.062.00010 (Box 62)
  - Council for National Policy, Paul Weyrich, 1995; MS074.002.062.00011 (Box 62)
  - Council for National Policy, youth council bios, 1993 -- 1998; MS074.002.062.00012 (Box 62)
  - Council for National Policy, speaker bios, 1993 -- 1995; MS074.002.062.00013 (Box 62)
  - Council for National Policy, biographies, 1996; MS074.002.062.00014 (Box 62)
  - Council for National Policy, member bios, 1993; MS074.002.062.00015 (Box 62)
  - Council for National Policy, new member bios, 1996; MS074.002.062.00016 (Box 62)
  - Council for National Policy, reports, 1995; MS074.002.062.00017 (Box 62)
  - Council for National Policy, member bios, 1995; MS074.002.062.00018 (Box 62)
  - Council for National Policy, five minute report, 1995 -- 1996; MS074.002.062.00019 (Box 62)
  - Council for National Policy, membership by state, 1996; MS074.002.062.00020 (Box 62)
  - Council for National Policy, correspondence from Austin Miles, 1996; MS074.002.062.00021 (Box 62)
  - Council for National Policy, biographies, 1996; MS074.002.062.00022 (Box 62)
  - Council for National Policy, notes, MS074.002.062.00023 (Box 62)
  - Council for National Policy, speaker biographies, 1996; MS074.002.062.00024 (Box 62)
  - Council for National Policy, material from meeting packet, 1993; MS074.002.062.00025 (Box 62)
  - Council for National Policy, guest biographies and program, 1996; MS074.002.062.00026 (Box 62)
  - Council for National Policy, accomplishments, 1994; MS074.002.062.00027 (Box 62)
  - Council for National Policy, notes, MS074.002.062.00028 (Box 62)
  - Council for National Policy, media contacts, 1995; MS074.002.062.00029 (Box 62)
  - Council for National Policy, gov. shutdown, 1995; MS074.002.062.00030 (Box 62)
  - Council for National Policy, persuading congressmen, 1995; MS074.002.062.00031 (Box 62)
  - Council for National Policy, weird science proposal, MS074.002.062.00032 (Box 62)
  - Council for National Policy, nomination form, 1995; MS074.002.062.00033 (Box 62)
  - Council for National Policy, rules, MS074.002.062.00034 (Box 62)
  - Council for National Policy, letters, 1994 -- 1995; MS074.002.062.00035 (Box 62)
  - Council for National Policy, congressional members, MS074.002.062.00036 (Box 62)
  - Council for National Policy, membership list and correspondence, 1996; MS074.002.062.00037 (Box 62)
  - Council for National Policy, 1985 -- 1994; MS074.002.062.00038 (Box 62)
  - Council for National Policy, article and press releast, 1996; MS074.002.062.00039 (Box 62)
  - Christian Coalition, Pat Robertson's extremist army, 1990 -- 1992; MS074.002.062.00040 (Box 62)
  - Christian Coalition, fact sheet, 1993 -- 1995; MS074.002.062.00041 (Box 62)
  - Christian Coalition, FEC v. CC, 1996; MS074.002.062.00042 (Box 62)
  - Christian Coalition, 1993 -- 1996; MS074.002.062.00043 (Box 62)
  - Christian Coalition, Catholic alliance, 1995; MS074.002.062.00044 (Box 62)
  - Christian Coalition, voter guides-general, 1995 -- 1996; MS074.002.062.00045 (Box 62)
  - Christian Coalition, voter guide '92, 1991 -- 1994; MS074.002.062.00046 (Box 62)
  - Christian Coalition, Christian American, 1992 -- 1994; MS074.002.062.00047 (Box 62)
  - Christian Coalition, healthcare, 1994; MS074.002.062.00048 (Box 62)
  - Christian Coalition, live, 1996; MS074.002.062.00049 (Box 62)
  - Christian Coalition, Capital Christian News, 1993 -- 1994; MS074.002.062.00050 (Box 62)
  - Christian Coalition, Founders Inn, 1992; MS074.002.062.00051 (Box 62)
  - Christian Coalition, leadership school, VA, 1993 -- 1995; MS074.002.062.00052 (Box 62)
  - Christian Coalition, articles about, 1995; MS074.002.062.00053 (Box 62)
  - Christian Coalition, congressional scorecard, 1993; MS074.002.062.00054 (Box 62)
  - Christian Coalition, new image, 1994; MS074.002.062.00055 (Box 62)
  - Christian Coalition, congressional scorecard, 1994; MS074.002.062.00056 (Box 62)
  - Christian Coalition, fundraising, 1996; MS074.002.062.00057 (Box 62)
  - Christian Coalition election/voter material, 1995; MS074.002.062.00058 (Box 62)